Guide to the Gerard Malanga Papers
Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library
- September 2009 acquisition, 1930s-2008; 18.68; (31 boxes) + 1 broadside folder
  - Oversize Material, 8
    - The Writer's Chronicle: Complaint (from Writing, Research, and Professional Files), 2007 (Box 150 (Oversize))
    - Malanga tearsheets of his photographs (from Printed and Publicity Material), 1990s (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - Periodicals (from Printed and Publicity Material), 1992-1993 (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - Interview magazine, featuring "Andy is 80!" (from Printed and Publicity Material), 2008 (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - Periodicals (from Printed and Publicity Material), 2000-2008 (Box 151 (Oversize))
    - Band À Part - Agnès B., press kit (from Printed and Publicity Material), undated (Box 152 (Oversize))
  - Artwork, 1968
    - Silkscreen by Charles Henri Ford, 1968 (Box 153 (Broadside))
  - Electronic and Audiovisual Media, 2005-2007
    - "At The Beach House: A Play by Aram Saroyan," compact disc, 2005 (Box 154)
    - "Star Ancestors: Guardians of the High Frontier," compact disc, 2007 (Box 154)
    - "Cap d'Agde, France", undated; 1 (Box 155, Item barcode 39002091394602)
      Restricted fragile material. Reference copies may be requested. Consult Access Services for further information.
    - Interview w/ Emma Lovetere and Annette O'Connor, original, 1990 January 19; 1 (Box 155, Item barcode 39002091394610)
- Printed material, 1.46; (2 boxes)
  - Printed material removed from September 2006 acquisition (Box A)
  - Printed material removed from September 2009 acquisition (Box B)